Guide to the Linda Mary Montano Papers MSS.386
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Non-commercially Released Media
  - Subseries B: Video recordings
    - "Seven Years of Living Art", undated; ID: 386.0428 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0428)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0429 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0429)
      "Linda M. Montano..'Seven Years of Living Art' Producer: Maida Barbour; 'Seven Stages of Intoxication' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon; 'The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon; 'The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano' Linda M. Montano with Andy Cochrun and Chris Erlon"
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, and The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0430 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0430)
      Originally under Montano's label "Compilation/Working Tapes."
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0431 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0431)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0432 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0432)
      Originally under Montano's label "Compilation Video and Audio."
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0433 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0433)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0434 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0434)
    - "Seven Years of Living Art, Seven Stages of Intoxication, The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna, The Seven Spiritual Lives of Linda M. Montano", undated; ID: 386.0435 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0435)
    - "Seven Years: Rough Edit Dub", undated; ID: 386.0436 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0436)
    - "Sex", undated; ID: 386.0437 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0437)
    - "Sex: 3 kinds", 1980; ID: 386.0438 (Box 67, Media ID: 386.0438)
      "Master Tape"
    - "Sex: From Annie Sprinkle", undated; ID: 386.0349 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0349)
      "Slow Motion Time"
    - "Sex One/Sex Two" Montano/Kolpan, 1986; ID: 386.0440 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0440)
      "32 minutes, 3/4" Master"
    - "Sister Jacques", September 10, 1981; ID: 386.0441 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0441)
    - "Sister Jacques Bernadette on The Live! Show", January 28, 1983; ID: 386.0442 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0442)
    - "Sister Jacques Edit: 7th and Summary Chakra", 1982; ID: 386.0443 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0443)
    - "Sister Jacques Edit: First 6 Chakras", undated; ID: 386.0444 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0444)
      "Master Edit"
    - "Sister Rose", undated; ID: 386.0445 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0445)
      "2nd is good"
    - "Sister Rose, Anorexia, Sister Jacques (4th Chakra), The End Is Near", undated; ID: 386.0446 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0446)
      "49:45, color."
    - "Sister Speaks: About Tenure, About the Priesthood, About Talking Nicely" Linda Montano, 1999; ID: 386.0447 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0447)
    - "Sister Speaks: About Tenure, About the Priesthood, About Talking Nicely" Linda Montano, 1999; ID: 386.0448 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0448)
    - "Spring '99 Work Sampler" Lara Davis, 1999; ID: 386.0449 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0449)
    - "Sprinkle PPM", undated; ID: 386.0450 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0450)
    - "The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna", undated; ID: 386.0451 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0451)
      "23:00"
    - "The Story of Sharada Wife of Ramakrishna: Raw Footage", undated; ID: 386.0452 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0452)
    - "Tarot at New Museum", undated; ID: 386.0453 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0453)
      "Transferred from H8mm"
    - "Television Appearances about Exorcism" Father James LeBar, undated; ID: 386.0454 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0454)
    - "Thank You Mrs. Mehta: Time Code", July 7, 2010; ID: 386.0455 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0455)
      "38 minutes"
    - "The Three of Me" Edna Floretta, undated; ID: 386.0456 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0456)
    - "Three Statements After September 11; Fairytale/Lifeists/Chakra Prayer", undated; ID: 386.0457 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0457)
      "3 Statements After 9/11: 1) Fairytale, 2) Lifeists/Artists, 3) Chakra/Sacrament Prayers"
    - "The Trial of the Sands of Time" Helene Aylon, 1989; ID: 386.0458 (Box 68, Media ID: 386.0458)
      "22 Minutes. Documentation: Myriam Abramowicz. with Linda Montano, Betty Parsons, Susan Griffin, Pauline Oliveros, Anna Halprin, Moira Roth, Peter Selz, Jim Melchert, Marc Kasky, Charles Shere, Myriam Abramowicz, Maryel Norris."
    - "Tones / Teresa", undated; ID: 386.0459 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0459)
    - "Two Aryuvedic Doctors", November 11, 2009; ID: 386.0461 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0461)
      "44 minutes"
    - "Two Aryuvedic Doctors", October 6, 2009; ID: 386.0460 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0460)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0462 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0462)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0463 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0463)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0464 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0464)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors", undated; ID: 386.0465 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0465)
    - "Two Ayruvedic Doctors: Midwife Interview Dr. A.L. Mehta", undated; ID: 386.0466 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0466)
    - "Valentine's Day", 1997; ID: 386.0467 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0467)
    - "Vivekananda: Healing" Linda Montano, undated; ID: 386.0468 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0468)
    - "Where the Deer and Antelope Play", undated; ID: 386.0469 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0469)
      "Music (mixed) - Ch.1"
    - "Why I am Not at Western Front", February 14, 2003; ID: 386.0470 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0470)
      "Linda Montano Video; 4"
    - "Why I'm Not at Your Birthday Party", August 2003; ID: 386.0471 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0471)
      "Malcha"
    - "Workshop Tuesday Performance: Nina and Garden", undated; ID: 386.0472 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0472)
      "for Rose"
  - Subseries C: Films
    - "Linda M. Montano: 11-22-93", November 22, 1993; ID: 386.0473 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0473)
      Original format: 8mm film.
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0474 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0474)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0475 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0475)
    - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.0476 (Box 69, Media ID: 386.0476)
- Series VIII: Data Storage
  This series contains DVD-R, CD-R, and floppy discs, primarily related to work on Montano's books. Related paper material can be found in Series I, Subseries B.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.
  - 2 Professional, Legal Contracts, ID: 386.3.0001 (Box 70, Folder 1, Media ID: 386.3.0001)
    Original format: 3 floppy discs.
  - 3 Interviews, undated; ID: 386.3.0002 (Box 70, Folder 2, Media ID: 386.3.0002)
  - 4 Catholic Information, undated; ID: 386.3.0003 (Box 70, Folder 3, Media ID: 386.3.0003)
    Original format: 4 floppy discs.
  - 5 Plays, undated; ID: 386.3.0004 (Box 70, Folder 4, Media ID: 386.3.0004)
    Original format: 1 floppy disc.
  - 5 Writings, undated; ID: 386.3.0005 (Box 70, Folder 5, Media ID: 386.3.0005)
  - 6 A Performance, undated; ID: 386.3.0006 (Box 70, Folder 6, Media ID: 386.3.0006)
  - 7A Dad Art, undated; ID: 386.3.0007 (Box 70, Folder 7, Media ID: 386.3.0007)
  - 8 Reprint of Art in Everyday Life, undated; ID: 386.3.0008 (Box 70, Folder 8, Media ID: 386.3.0008)
  - 9 Letters of Linda M. Montano, undated; ID: 386.3.0009 (Box 70, Folder 9, Media ID: 386.3.0009)
  - 10 Misc. "Forget This Seems to be Jennie Sorkin Stuff", undated; ID: 386.3.0010 (Box 70, Folder 10, Media ID: 386.3.0010)
  - Academia Deconst. Tenure, undated; ID: 386.3.0011 (Box 70, Folder 11, Media ID: 386.3.0011)
  - Angelika Festa: Shall We Talk?, 1997-1998; ID: 386.3.0012 (Box 70, Folder 12, Media ID: 386.3.0012)
  - Copulating Couple for LOVE SEX, undated; ID: 386.3.0013 (Box 70, Folder 13, Media ID: 386.3.0013)
    Original format: 2 floppy discs.
  - Email, undated; ID: 386.3.0014 (Box 70, Folder 14, Media ID: 386.3.0014)
  - Food, Sex, Money, Death LM Resume, undated; ID: 386.3.0015 (Box 70, Folder 15, Media ID: 386.3.0015)
  - Food Sex Money Death, Mill 1, May 1992; ID: 386.3.0016 (Box 70, Folder 16, Media ID: 386.3.0016)
  - Friends Forever: The NY Reunion, September 2002; ID: 386.3.0017 (Box 70, Folder 17, Media ID: 386.3.0017)
    Original format: CD-R.
  - Jennifer Howard Grad School, undated; ID: 386.3.0018 (Box 70, Folder 18, Media ID: 386.3.0018)
  - Laura Cottingham "Fame & Money", undated; ID: 386.3.0019 (Box 70, Folder 19, Media ID: 386.3.0019)
  - Linda, undated; ID: 386.3.0020 (Box 70, Folder 20, Media ID: 386.3.0020)
  - Linda Intro by Annie Sprinkle, undated; ID: 386.3.0021 (Box 70, Folder 21, Media ID: 386.3.0021)
  - Linda Montano.doc from Kara Reilly NYU, undated; ID: 386.3.0022 (Box 70, Folder 22, Media ID: 386.3.0022)
  - Linda M. Montano Gentle At Last Performance Documentation, October 2006; ID: 386.3.0023 (Box 70, Folder 23, Media ID: 386.3.0023)
  - Linda Release, undated; ID: 386.3.0024 (Box 70, Folder 24, Media ID: 386.3.0024)
  - Linda Resume, etc., undated; ID: 386.3.0025 (Box 70, Folder 25, Media ID: 386.3.0025)
  - Montano Book, undated; ID: 386.3.0026 (Box 70, Folder 26, Media ID: 386.3.0026)
    Original format: 2 Zip 100.
  - Neil Graduation Madison Birthday, May 24, 2001; ID: 386.3.0027 (Box 70, Folder 27, Media ID: 386.3.0027)
  - Peter Ketter's Recommendation Letter, undated; ID: 386.3.0028 (Box 70, Folder 28, Media ID: 386.3.0028)
  - Photos, undated; ID: 386.3.0029 (Box 70, Folder 29, Media ID: 386.3.0029)
  - [Moira] Roth/Food Intro + Bio, March 1998; ID: 386.3.0030 (Box 70, Folder 30, Media ID: 386.3.0030)
  - Sheelah Murthy MFA, undated; ID: 386.3.0031 (Box 70, Folder 31, Media ID: 386.3.0031)
  - Transmedia, undated; ID: 386.3.0032 (Box 70, Folder 32, Media ID: 386.3.0032)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0033 (Box 70, Folder 33, Media ID: 386.3.0033)
    Original format: 1 CD-R; 1 floppy disc.
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0034 (Box 70, Folder 34, Media ID: 386.3.0034)
  - Untitled, undated; ID: 386.3.0035 (Box 70, Folder 35, Media ID: 386.3.0035)
  - "What Kind of Software Was Used to Create This", 1992-1998; ID: 386.3.0036 (Box 70, Folder 36, Media ID: 386.3.0036)
  - Writings 1-10 as seen in Brown Book, 2007; ID: 386.3.0037 (Box 70, Folder 37, Media ID: 386.3.0037)
  - Writings by Edna Floretta, undated; ID: 386.3.0038 (Box 70, Folder 38, Media ID: 386.3.0038)
- Series IX: Objects
  This series consists of objects that were made by or belonged to Montano. The objects are arranged to reflect the overall arrangement of the collection.
  These objects are arranged to reflect the overall series order.
  - Linda Montano Keychain, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0001)
  - Linda Montano Keychain: "For a Thrill Look...", undated (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0003)
  - Seven Years of Living Art/Seven Chakras framed miniature portraits, undated (Box 83, Object ID: 386.2.0028)
  - LOVESICK Barsoap, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0004)
  - "My Way of Life Pocket Edition of St. Thomas", undated (Box 119, Object ID: 386.2.0006)
  - "Daily Missal of the Mystical Body", November 16, 1956 (Box 119, Object ID: 386.2.0007)
  - Holy Bible from Dr. Mehta, December 25, 1994 (Box 119, Object ID: 386.2.0008)
  - "The Liber Usualis", 1959 (Box 119, Object ID: 386.2.0009)
  - Montano Performance Piece: Word Association, undated (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0010)
  - "Photo-a-day by Linda Montano" Kodak case, 1974 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0011)
  - Woodcut Form 1, undated (Box 118, Object ID: 386.2.0023)
  - Woodcut Form 2, undated (Box 118, Object ID: 386.2.0024)
  - Woodcut Form 3, undated (Box 118, Object ID: 386.2.0025)
  - Woodcut Form 4, undated (Box 118, Object ID: 386.2.0026)
  - Annie Sprinkle ceramic bowl in velvet bag, January 1, 1995 (Box 72, Object ID: 386.2.0019)
  - "Annie Sprinkle's Post-Modern Pin-Ups: Pleasure Activist Playing Cards", undated (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0002)
  - Annie Sprinkle purple barrette, undated (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0018)
  - Tehching Hsieh's wallet, undated (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0005)
  - Small figure in plastic rectangle, 1998 (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0012)
  - Small yellow ceramic dog head, undated (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0013)
  - Ceramic clock and fork by R. Howland, 1986 (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0014)
  - Henry J. Montano Bank Plaque, February 1969 (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0015)
  - Subscription Opus Issue 18: Jude Weirmeir, undated (Box 71, Object ID: 386.2.0016)
  - Red cotton dinner napkin puppet, February 1998 (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0017)
  - "A Bag Book" by Betsy Damon, February 9, 1983 (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0020)
  - Eraser performance art piece, undated (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0021)
  - "The Perpetual Napkin" by Barbara Smith, 1981 (Box 117, Object ID: 386.2.0022)
  - Hannah Wilke Gum Sculpture, undated (Box 80, Object ID: 386.2.0027)
  - "Free Art-Life Counseling" Sign, undated (Box Shared Fales 093, Folder 3)
- Series X: Library, 1931-2013; 6 Linear Feet in 5 record cartons and 2 manuscript boxes.
  This series contains books, periodicals, exhibition catalogues, and other print material owned by Montano. Some print materials originally donated by Montano were removed during processing and are searchable via the library catalog.
  - Allsopp, Ric and deLahunta, Scott (Eds.). The connected body?: an interdisciplinary approach to the body and performance. Amsterdam: Amsterdam School of the Arts, 1996 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - Antim, Eleanor. Being Antinova. Los Angeles: Astro Artz, 1983 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - Atkins, Robert. ArtSpeak: a guide to contemporary ideas, movements, and buzzwords. New York: Abbeville Press Publishers, 1990 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - Baas, Jacquelynn and Jacob, Mary Jane. Buddha mind in contemporary art. Berkeley: University of California Press, 2004 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - Baker, Jo-Anne (Ed.). Sex tips & tales from Women Who Dare. Alameda, CA; Hunter House, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Jo-Anne (Ed.). Sex tips: advice from women experts around the world. Australia: Allen & Unwin, 1999 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - Belloq, E.J. Storyville portraits; photographs from the New Orleans red-light district, circa 1912. New York: Museum of Modern Art; distributed by New York Graphic Society, Greenwich, CT, 1970 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - Bloch, Ricardo and Celender, Don. Mortal Remains. New York: OK Harris Gallery, 1995 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - Breitwieser, Sabine (Ed.). Double Life: Identity And Transformation In Contemporary Art. Wien: Generali Foundation, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - Bucci, Mario. Giotto. New York: Grosset & Dunlap, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - Carr, C. On edge: performance at the end of the twentieth century. Hanover, NH: Wesleyan University Press, 1993 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art. Outside the Frame: Performance and the Object. Cleveland, OH: Cleveland Center for Contemporary Art, 1994 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - Craighead, Meinrad. The mother's songs: images of God the mother. New York: Paulist Press, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - Crowne, Melchia. Sky cycle/Earth ring, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Doyle, Jennifer. Hold it against me: difficulty and emotion in contemporary art. Durham; London: Duke University Press, 2013 (Box 96, Folder 15)
  - Drobnick, Jim; Fisher, Jennifer. Museopathy. Agnes Etherington Art Centre, 2001 (Box 96, Folder 16)
  - Estevez, Nicolas Dumit, (Ed.). Life as material for art and vice versa. New York: Queens Museum of Art, 2011 (Box 96, Folder 17)
  - Evans, Bessie and Evans, May G. American Indian Dance Steps. New York, A. S. Barnes & Co, Inc., 1931 (Box 96, Folder 18)
  - Fitzgerald, f/Stop. Documentia. San Francisco: Last Gasp of San Francisco, 1987 (Box 96, Folder 19)
  - Fernett, Gene. A Thousand Golden Horns. Midland, MI: Pendell Company, 1966 (Box 96, Folder 20)
  - Fisher, Jennifer. Technologies of intuition. Toronto: YYZ Books, 2006 (Box 96, Folder 21)
  - Gamper, Gisela and Pollack, Rachel. Fabrications. Barrytown, NY: Barrytown Ltd., 1997 (Box 96, Folder 22)
  - Glass, Liz, Magers, Susannah, and Myers, Julian. Give Them The Picture: An Anthology of La Mamelle and ART COM 1975-1984. CCA Wattis Institute for Contemporary Arts, undated (Box 96, Folder 23)
  - Graves, Ken and Payne, Mitchell. American Snapshots. Oakland, CA: Scrimshaw Press, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 24)
  - Hammond, Harmony. Wrappings: Essays on Feminism, Art, and the Martial Arts. New York: TSL Press, 1984 (Box 96, Folder 25)
  - Haines, Frank. Frank exchanges. [place of publication unknown: publisher unknown], 2014 (Box 96, Folder 26)
  - Hay, Deborah. My body, the Buddhist. Hanover, N.H.: University Press of New England; Wesleyan University Press, 2000 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - Hay, Deborah. Lamb at the altar: The story of a dance. Durham, NC: Duke University Press, 1994 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - Highwater, Jamake. Ritual of the wind: North American Indian Ceremonies, Music, and Dances. New York: The Viking Press, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - Huffman, Kathy Rae. Video: a retrospective: Long Beach Museum of Art, 1974-1984. Long Beach, CA: Long Beach Museum of Art (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - Kastner, Jeffrey. Nature. London: Whitechapel Gallery; Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 2012 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - Keyes, Ken, Jr. Taming Your Mind. Berkeley: Living Love Center, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - LeBar, James J., Rev. Cults, sects, and the new age. Huntingdon, IN: Our Sunday Visitor Publishing Division, 1989 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - LeSueur, Meridel. Rites of Ancient Ripening. Minneapolis: Vanilla Press Inc., 1975 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - Lewallen, Constance. Space, time, sound: conceptual art in the San Francisco Bay Area, the 1970s. San Francisco: San Francisco Museum of Modern Art, 1981 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - Lewallen, Constance M. and Moss, Karen. State of Mind: New California Art circa 1970. Berkeley: University of California Press, 2011 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - Loeffler, Carl E and Tong, Darlene. Performance anthology: source book for a decade of California performance art. San Francisco, CA: Contemporary Arts Press, 1980 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - Marioni, Tom. Sculptures and Installations: 1969-1997, undated (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - Mark, Lisa Gabrielle and Schimmel, Paul. Under the Big Black Sun: California Art 1974-1981. Los Angeles: Museum of Contemporary Art; Munich: DelMonico Books, Prestel, 2011 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Marranca, Bonnie. Performance Histories. New York: PAJ Publications, 2007 (Box 97, Folder 14)
  - Mendieta, Ana. Ana Mendieta: She Got Love. Milano, Italy: Skira, 2013 (Box 97, Folder 15)
  - Merali, Shaheen (Ed.). New York: states of mind: art in the city. London: Saqi, 2008 (Box 97, Folder 16)
  - Miller, Lynn C., Taylor, Jacqueline, and Carver, Heather (Eds.). Voices made flesh: performing women's autobiography. Madison, WI: University of Wisconsin Press, 2003 (Box 97, Folder 17)
  - Montano, Linda. The Art/Life Institute Handbook. Saugerties, NY: Arts/Life Institute, 1988 (Box 97, Folder 18)
  - Montano, Linda. You too are a performance artists. Santa Fe, NM: SITE Santa Fe, 2013 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Myers, Roger. Guide to archival materials of the center for creative photography. Tuscon, Arizona, University of Arizona, 1986 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - Nemec, Vernita. Private Thoughts/Private Places, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - Norman, Howard A. The Wishing Bone Cycle. New York, Stonehill Publishing Company, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - Oliveros, Pauline. The roots of the moment. New York: Drogue Press, 1998 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - Oliveros, Pauline. Software for people: collected writings 1963-80. Baltimore, MD: Smith Publications; Barrytown, NY: Printed Editions, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - Oliveros, Pauline and Cohen, Becky. Initiation Dream. Los Angeles, Astro Artz, 1981 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - Phillips, Lisa. The American Century: Art & Culture, 1950-2000. New York: Whitney Museum of American Art in association with Norton, 1999 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - Re/Search Publications. Angry Women. Re/Search Publications, 1991 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - Reigns, Steven. Your dead body is my welcome mat. Burning Page Press, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - Reigns, Steven (Ed.). My life is poetry: an anthology of writings by gay, lesbian, and bisexual seniors. Los Angeles: Grenadier Press, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - Richman, Gary. Offset: a survey of artists' books. Cambridge, MA: New England Foundation for the Arts, 1984 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - Rosen, Randy and Brawer, Catherine C. Making their mark: women artists move into the mainstream, 1970-85. New York: Abbeville Press, 1989 (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - Roth, Moira. The amazing decade: women and performance art in America, 1970-1980. Los Angeles: Astro Artz, 1983 (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - Roth, Moira (Ed.). Connecting Conversations: Interviews with 28 Bay Area Women Artists. Oakland, CA: Eucalyptus Press Mills College, 1988 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome. Technicians of the sacred: A range of poetries from Africa, America, Asia, Europe & Oceania. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1985 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - Rothenberg, Jerome. Poetics & Polemics: 1980-2005. Tuscaloosa, AL: University of Alabama Press, 2008 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - Rugoff, Ralph. Extra art: a survey of artists' ephemera, 1960-1999. Santa Monica: Smart Art Press, 2001 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - Sands. Profeminist WHITE FLOWERS, 2007 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - Schneemann, Carolee. Imaging her erotics: essays, interviews, projects. Cambridge, MA: MIT Press, 2002 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - Schroeder, Johannes Lothar. Blende und traumzeit. Kiel: NONOMPRESS, 1992 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - Shigemi, Inaga. Questioning Oriental Aesthetics and Thinking: Conflicting Vision of "Asia" under the Colonial Empire. Kyoto, International Research Center for Japanese Studies, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Terry. Contemporary Art: World Currents. Upper Saddle River, NJ: Prentice Hall, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - Solomon-Godeau, Abigail, Montano, Linda, Princenthal, Nancy, and Sabbatino, Mary. Ana Mendieta: Blood & Fire. Paris/New York: Galerie LeLong, undated (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - Tisdall, Caroline, and Beuys, Joseph. Joseph Beuys. Thames and Hudson, London, for the Guggenheim Museum, New York, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - Vera, Veronica. Miss Vera's finishing school for boys who want to be girls. New York: Doubleday, 1997 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - Villines, Melanie. Windy City Sinners: a novel. Chicago, IL: Inklings Press, 2011 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - Villines, Melanie. Tales of the Sacred Heart: a novel. Libertyville, IL: Bogfire, 1999 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - Vincent, Stephen and Zweig, Ellen. The Poetry reading: a contemporary compendium on language & performance. San Francisco: Momo's Press, 1981 (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - Von Gunden, Heidi. The music of Pauline Oliveros. Metuchen, NJ: Scarecrow Press, 1983 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - Wark, Jayne. Radical gestures feminism and performance art in North America. Montreal: McGill-Queen's University Press, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Warr, Tracey and Jones, Amelia. The artist's body. London: Phaidon, 2000 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - Weintraub, Linda and Schuckmann, Skip. ECOcentric Topics: pioneering themes for eco-art. Rhinebeck, NY: ArtNow Publications, 2006 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - Wexler, Alice. Art education beyond the classroom: pondering the outsider and other sites of learning. New York; Houndmills, Basingstoke, Hampshire England: Palgrave Macmillan, 2012 (Box 99, Folder 12)